{
  "name": "Indian and International Systems of Numeration",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per Indian numeration:\n325047",
      "answers": ["THREE LAKH TWENTY FIVE THOUSAND AND FORTY SEVEN"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per Indian numeration:\n447896",
      "answers": ["FOUR LAKH FORTY SEVEN THOUSAND EIGHT HUNDRED AND NINETY SIX"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per Indian numeration:\n752368",
      "answers": ["SEVEN LAKH FIFTY TWO THOUSAND THREE HUNDRED AND SIXTY EIGHT"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per Indian numeration:\n1478965",
      "answers": ["FOURTEEN LAKH SEVENTY EIGHT THOUSAND NINE HUNDRED AND SIXTY FIVE"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per International numeration:\n652104",
      "answers": ["SIX HUNDRED FIFTY TWO THOUSAND ONE HUNDRED AND FOUR"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per International numeration:\n412589",
      "answers": ["FOUR HUNDRED TWELVE THOUSAND FIVE HUNDRED AND EIGHTY NINE"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per International numeration:\n602583",
      "answers": ["SIX HUNDRED TWO THOUSAND FIVE HUNDRED AND EIGHTY THREE"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number in words as per International numeration:\n963258",
      "answers": ["NINE HUNDRED SIXTY THREE THOUSAND TWO HUNDRED AND FIFTY EIGHT"],
      "keyboard": "capital_alphabets",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number separating the periods with commas as per International numeration:\nTWO HUNDRED FOUR THOUSAND SIX HUNDRED AND ONE",
      "answers": ["204,601"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number separating the periods with commas as per International numeration:\nONE MILLION TWO HUNDRED FOUR THOUSAND ONE HUNDRED AND ONE",
      "answers": ["1,204,101"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the following number separating the periods with commas as per International numeration:\nSEVEN MILLION FOUR HUNDRED AND SEVEN",
      "answers": ["7,000,407"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    }
  ]
}